<scenarios>
    <scenario
	id="1"
	name="Dullsville"
	year="1900"
	tagline="Boredom"
    >
        <description>Things haven't changed much around here in the last hundred years or so and the residents are beginning to get bored. They think Dullsville could be the next great city with the right leader. It is your job to attract new growth and development, turning Dullsville into a Metropolis within 30 years.</description>
    </scenario>
    <scenario
	id="2"
	name="San Francsico"
	year="1906"
	tagline="Earthquake"
    >
        <description>Damage from the earthquake was minor compared to that of the ensuing fires, which took days to control. 1500 people died. Controlling the fires should be your initial concern. Then clear the rubble and start rebuilding. You have 5 years.</description>
    </scenario>
    <scenario
	id="3"
	name="Hamburg"
	year="1944"
	tagline="Bombing"
    >
        <description>Allied fire-bombing of German cities in WWII caused tremendous damage and loss of life. People living in the inner cities were at greatest risk. You must control the firestorms during the bombing and then rebuild the city after the war. You have 5 years.</description>
    </scenario>
    <scenario
	id="4"
	name="Bern"
	year="1965"
	tagline="Traffic"
    >
        <description>The roads here are becoming more congested every day, and the residents are upset. They demand that you do something about it. Some have suggested a mass transit system as the answer, but this would require major rezoning in the downtown area. You have 10 years.</description>
    </scenario>
    <scenario
	id="5"
	name="Tokyo"
	year="1957"
	tagline="Monster Attack"
    >
        <description>A large reptilian creature has been spotted in the water. It seems to be attracted to areas of high pollution. There is a trail of destruction wherever it goes. All you can do is wait till he leaves, then rebuild from the rubble.</description>
    </scenario>
    <scenario
	id="6"
	name="Detroit"
	year="1972"
	tagline="Crime"
    >
        <description>By 1970, competition from overseas and other economic factors pushed the once &quot;automobile capital of the world&quot; into recession. Plummeting land values and unemployment then increased crime in the inner-city to chronic levels. You have 10 years to reduce crime and rebuild the industrial base of the city.</description>
    </scenario>
    <scenario
	id="7"
	name="Boston"
	year="2010"
	tagline="Nuclear Meltdown"
    >
        <description>A major meltdown is about to occur at one of the new downtown nuclear reactors. The area in the vicinity of the reactor will be severly contaminated by radiation, forcing you to restructure the city around it. You have 5 years to get the situation under control.</description>
    </scenario>
    <scenario
	id="8"
	name="Rio de Janeiro"
	year="2047"
	tagline="Coastal Flooding"
    >
        <description>In the mid-21st century, the greenhouse effect raised global temperatures 6 degrees F. Polar icecaps melted and raised sea levels worldwide. Coastal areas were devastated by flood and erosion. You have 10 years to turn this swamp back into a city again.</description>
    </scenario>
</scenarios>
